「コルコ王女のミイラ」が 競売にかけられる。
how frustrating
イワレンコフ トチーノ　ヴェーゼ
weakness could be!
で　俺達は？
Gon...
バショウとリンセンは 裏口側の監視だ。
For the thirty days that you can't use Nen...
クラピカとセンリツは 正面口側の監視。
I'll protect you.
スクワラと俺は お嬢様の護衛だ。
I will do whatever it takes!
マフィアンコミュニティーが仕切る 地下競売を 何者かが狙っているという 情報を得た　ノストラードファミリー
Colt arrived, under a white flag of
surrender, to ask the Hunters a favor. His wish was that they save the dying Queen.
そのボディーガードとして 雇われたクラピカ達は
After hearing his request, Morel and
Knov took Colt to see Netero.
それぞれの任務に就いていた
It's me. Send over a team of Chimera Ant
researchers immediately.
勢ぞろいだなぁ。
We leave in four hours.
何がだ？ たかが競売でしょ？ 代理人に頼めば いいんじゃないの？
We will do everything we can.
ここは メンツ争いの場でもあるのさ。
Colt-kun...
落札すれば 価格の５％が手数料として
We'll need your cooperation.
落札価格が高いほど その額も大きい。 ああ。
Heart This may be the last time I wear this...
そうやって　自分達の経済力を示し マフィアに名を売る。
Hey, is that... Yes, it's his "heart" T-shirt.
つまり　自分達の株を上げる チャンスってわけね。
Heart
だが　そのせいで あまりの高額で落札しちまって
They say it's a lucky shirt he only
wears when he fights for real.
破綻した組もあるって話だ。
But I always thought it was a just a rumor...
フッ。 そろそろ　始まる時間だ。
Colt-kun, it appears that you can use Nen...
え
It feels like needles pricking
me all over my body.
皆様　ようこそ お集まりいただきました。
Most likely, you will be unable to lay a finger on him.
それでは　堅苦しい挨拶は 抜きにして。
You'll be killed by one of his Royal Guard before you can get close enough.
あっ。 あっ。
I see...
くたばりな！
I'm happy to hear that.
うわ！
At this age, I'll be a challenger. This is exciting stuff.
伏せろ！
Morel, I believe your disciples
were to fight today, yes?
風船黒子よ！　俺をガードせよ！
Yes. Take the victors and the research team, along with Colt, to the nest.
うっ…　これは…
I'm off to see an old acquaintance.
機関銃の　たかが一発一発が 何て威力だ！
Don't forget to pay me my one million.
逃げろ！　早くボスに知らせ…。
I know.
ハッ！
What are you talking about?
ヴェーゼ　お前は先に行け…。
Everyone else has left.
ギョギョ。
Though a few oddballs did leave
their squadrons to stay here.
うっ…。
I suppose it's fortunate no fighting broke out.
呆気ねえ　呆気ねえ。
Unfortunately, it won't work.
頼むぜ　シズク。
Chimera Ants from different generations
are completely different organisms.
うん　行くよ　デメちゃん。
Just look at how much the Chimera
Ants in your own generation vary.
ギョギョギョ。
But the sentiment is appreciated.
この部屋中の散乱した死体と その血
We'll do our best, so pray...
肉片および死人の所持品全てを 吸い取れ！ ついでに椅子も。
That, miraculously, all the organs will function.
て…　てめぇら…　何者だ？ まぁ　いい。
Pray... Is that all I can do?
誰であろうと…　皆殺しだ。
Someone...
コミュニティーが必ず
Is anyone there?
てめぇらを！　その家族を！
Yes, I am by your side!
辱め…　切り刻み
Please give me your command! What is it?
地獄の苦しみ…。
Telepathy? Yes, the Queen cannot speak as we do.
家族？　何それ。
Perhaps she has a hint for saving her life. My son...
うまく聞き取れないけど ビルの中が騒がしいわ。
Did he have any defects? ...defects?
何か　あったな リーダーに連絡を！
You have nothing to worry about.
分かった リンセン達には　俺から連絡する。
He is perfectly healthy, and right now...
お前達は オークション会場へ向かえ！
And right now, he's taken
the Royal Guard to search for medicine to help you.
な…　何だ？
...to help you.
人っ子一人いねえ。 どこ行ったんだ？　捜せ！
The truth is that, after he killed
and ate Squadron Leaders, he left in search of a new territory.
おい！　競売品は　どうなってる。
I doubt he will return.
地下だ！　地下へ急げ！
He ate them? The King
どうやら　オークション会場にいた人間が 全て消えたらしい。
has no concern for the Queen's health!
[TEL]　何!? 会場は　ちょっとしたパニックだ。
Then, the King is safe?
[TEL]　収拾がつかない状況に なっている。
Yes.
それで 競売品は　どうなっている？
That is wonderful...
[TEL]　今　センリツが地下の金庫に…。
Oh, no.
か…　空っぽだ…。 今日の分の競売品 全部　盗まれている！
Send the King off at once.
一体　誰が？ クソ！ どこへ消えやがったんだ！ 手分けして捜せ　バカ野郎！
There is no time to waste on my well-being...
とにかく　全組織に 情報を流せ！　早くしろ！ よし　分かった。
My son has the potential to rule the world.
絶対に俺達で盗っ人を捕まえる！ 俺も今から　そっちへ向かう。
He was born too early, so I was very worried.
ビル裏手の中央公園で リンセン達と合流だ。 スクワラ。 はい！
However, it appears...
念のため 犬を５頭ほど残しておけ。
I have fulfilled my duty...
俺達が戻るまで 誰も部屋に入れるなよ！ はい。 はい。
That was all I wanted.
道路という道路は 全て封鎖した
What are you saying?!
あと考えられるのは　空だ！
You are our guiding light...
不審な飛行船を見つけたら 連絡しろ！ いいか！　見つけても殺すなよ！
Without you, the rest of us will
lose our way and perish.
コミュニティーから 「捕まえた組には 莫大な褒美を出す」と 連絡があった！ いいか！ 必ず　生かして連れて来い！
I know my body better than anyone else...
[TEL]　ああ　金庫の中には 何ひとつ入ってなかった。
However, I have
唯一　事情を知ってた オークショニアによると
no regrets. Please stop!
一度　金庫の中に入れた品を 数時間前に
I beg you... Please live!
また　どこかへ移したらしい。 まるで　あらかじめ こういう事態が
Use my body! Please! Give it a shot!
起こることを知ってたみたいに。
Until you try, you don't know it won't work!
ほぉ…。
Listen...
あまりにもタイミングが 良過ぎるとは思わないか？
You must listen to what the Queen has to say.
俺達の中に ユダがいるぜ。
I have one last request...
俺達の中に　ユダがいるぜ。
I thought of a name... for my son.
[TEL]　いないよ　そんな奴は。
Meruem.
それに俺の考えじゃ ユダは裏切り者じゃ　ない。 ちなみに　ユダは銀３０枚で キリストを売ったとされているが
It means the light that illuminates all.
俺達の中の裏切り者は いくらで　俺達をマフィアに売る？
Deliver my message to him...
メリットを考えろ。 マフィアに俺達を売って そいつは　何を得るんだ？ 金か？　名誉か？　地位か？
My beloved son...
[TEL]　それと　もう１つ 解せない点がある。 ん？
I failed to protect her again...
密告者がいたとすると あまりにも対応が中途半端だ。 Ａ級首の俺達が 競売品を狙いに来るって情報が 本当に入っていたら
I can't protect anyone...
もう少し厳重に警備してても いいんじゃないか？
Has something like this happened before?
[TEL] 客のほうは何も知らされず
No, he's probably referring to a memory
丸腰で集まってたんだろ？
from when he was human.
そう言われれば…。
You have memories from
when you were human?
俺の結論を言うと…。
Of course, though naturally, some
remember more than others...
情報提供者はいるが その内容は具体的ではない。
Our human personalities strongly influence our current behavior.
にもかかわらず それを信用している人物が マフィアンコミュニティーの 上層部にいる。
And many can remember their human names.
よく分からねえな。
Otherwise, it wouldn't have been
as easy to learn to speak.
死ぬまで 「知らない」の一点張りだったぜ。
Hmm?
フェイタンが体に聞いたから 間違いない。
Th-This is...
彼が今日一番 気の毒な人だったね。
There's...
[TEL]　移動場所を知ってる奴の 情報は　聞き出したんだろう？
There's something moving!
もちろんだ。
Don't touch it!
地下競売を仕切る マフィアンコミュニティーの元締は
I will... I will remove it.
金庫には　「陰獣」のメンバーが たった１人で来たそうだぜ。
I shall protect this child...
その日の競売品が　ぎっしりと 置いてあったらしいが…。
This time, I won't fail...
シズクと同じタイプの 念能力者か。
Morel?
[TEL]　恐らくな。
Colt...
向こうも ５００人近い客が消えたことで 気づいたはずだ。
Can you promise me that you and that child
will never eat humans?
殺っちまっていいよな？ [TEL]　もちろんだ 追っ手相手に 適当に暴れてやれよ。
If you can't make that promise, you should get out of my sight immediately.
[TEL]　そうすれば 奴らのほうから姿を現すさ。
But if you're willing to give your word...
フフフ…　楽しみだぜ！ あれだ！ 見つけたぞ　気球だ！
No one will ever lay a finger on you, not as long as I'm around.
気球が　ゴルドー砂漠方面に向かって 移動中！　追跡します！
You have my promise!
もしかしたら
It isn't a big deal...
敵は　ただの武装強盗集団じゃ ねえかもしれねぇ。 「十老頭」に連絡！ 大至急　「陰獣」の出動を要請しろ。
I inherited my soft nature from my master.
待て！
Okay, I've recovered! Knuckle and the other Hunters will save Kite.
客をさらったのは　てめぇらか？ ええ。
Ah, so you do understand.
この場面でも　ええ根性してるな。 てめぇらの頭は　どいつだ？
You may have met Kite before we did, but we've spent more time with him.
イイイ…。 てめぇ！
After we crossed the mountains, if you'd still
been moping, I would've given you a beating...
あっ。
And told you that Kite wouldn't
want to see you two like this.
アハハハ…。 えっ？　えぇ…。
I know he's still alive, and he doesn't want you to have regrets.
うぅ…。 うぉ！
There's enough space here
for squats and push-ups. Yeah, you're right.
何よりも強く ただ強くってのが
Hey, Spin...
あいつの信条だからな。
Hmm? Why do you want to be a Hunter?
ただの銃じゃ　ウボォーの体に かすり傷ひとつ　つけられんぜ。
I need the money to repay a huge debt.
まるで ゴリラ対アリだな　ありゃ。
Have you heard of the small-billed swan?
おっ　まだ来るぜ！ わざわざ殺されに ご苦労なこった。
It's a species of bird that can only live
in the area around a certain mine.
見てても仕方ないから トランプでもしないか？
No one knows why that is.
そうね。 賛成。
Is it the water? The food? The weather?
ボス！ うん。
So I bought the entire area where the mine is.
フン…。
Kite provided the money for that.
これじゃあ　「陰獣」が現れるまでの 準備運動にもなりゃしねえ。
He was the first adult who was willing to listen
痛ってぇ！
Stinn and I were born in that area.
あっ。 あっ！
The sight of thousands of small-billed swans taking
flight with the light of dawn at their backs...
おし！　命中だ！ そこまでだ！
That's the oldest, but strongest,
memory Stinn and I have.
いい気になってんじゃねえぞ この化け物が！ 戦車も１発で　おしゃかにしちまう このスーパーバズーカ砲で 粉々になれや！
When we heard the area would be demolished, we realized how important it was to us...
悲しいぜ…。
Kite said that he envied us.
俺は　たかが戦車と同じ評価かよ。
He doesn't have a home.
死ね！
Because he doesn't know where he was born.
やったか？
Once this mission is over,
I can show you two
あいつ…　人を紙くずみてぇに ちぎってやがるぞ！
Th-This is...
いつの間にか　心音が
Goal!
俺は「陰獣」の蚯蚓 お前ら　どこの組の者だ？
Given Cheetu's speed, he's probably
already crossed the border. Well, I'll take my time searching...
ノストラードファミリーに 雇われているボディーガードだ。
For my own paradise,
with plenty of food and females.
なるほど　少しは「念」が 使えるようだが　やめときな。
Cows, pigs, humans, boars, bears...
あいつらは ただのコソ泥じゃ　ない。
I'll take any of those if they're plentiful.
殺しが 生活の一部みたいなもんだ。 い…　いわば 殺しのプロだな　うん。
Because I am the Glutton King.
餅は餅屋ってな。
The Chimera Ants that were once soldiers
病犬。 俺は　蛭。
have now departed to become kings.
こいつらが…　「陰獣」
Meanwhile, the King
地下競売を襲った連中への 報復に マフィアンコミュニティーは 「陰獣」を放った
is now in the Republic of East Gorteau.